jennyvien94@gmail.com • (415) 298-9812 • https://jennyvien.myportfolio.com/

PROFILE

Web developer dedicated to helping people and small businesses design and build custom, user-friendly, mobile-responsive websites. Experienced with Wordpress, Elementor, and Adobe XD. Optimistically inclined and driven to learn software and technology to get the job done.

SKILLS & ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Web Design and Development | Responsive Design | Wordpress | Elementor | Adobe XD | Adobe Photoshop & Lightroom | Catalog Content Management | HTML/CSS/Javascript

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Developer & Counter Help | Fillmore Bakeshop, San Francisco, CA November 2019 - Present

- Redesign and develop the bakery's website using Elementor and WordPress launching May 2021.
- Create documentation and videos to train team on how to maintain website and update site content.
- Efficiently and accurately prepare pastries and drink orders for customers daily.
- Perform tasks necessary for optimal bakery operations, including but not limited to constructing pastry boxes, restocking supplies, cleaning counters, and janitorial duties.

Junior UI/UX Designer| Cut2lt, Remote

December 2019 - July 2020

- Redesigned the people management dashboard for their video content management system.
- Performed user research and created user stories, personas and storyboards to support design process.
- Worked closely with the engineering team to iterate design based on feedback.

Catalog Content Coordinator | Instacart, San Francisco, CA

October 2019 - March 2020

- Performed quality assurance audits and resolved product inaccuracies to ensure web storefront reflected the highest standards.
- Collaborated with the CPG team to clean up product data for scheduled promotional campaigns.
- Applied categorical and tax codes information to over 4000 products using Google Sheets to improve the search and navigation experience of beverages.

Shift Lead | Instacart, San Francisco, CA

March 2018 - October 2019

- Led Instacart in-store operations at the highest volume warehouse locations in San Francisco to exceed productivity and quality metrics week over week.
- Prioritized issues and resolve problems with a sense of urgency and composure in a fast-paced environment.
- Performed contextual inquiries to identify areas of opportunities and drive process improvements.
- Analyzed data to create weekly plans to coach shoppers. Maintained coaching schedule in Google Calendar and collaborated with shoppers to develop and implement strategies to achieve metrics.

EDUCATION

Udemy May 2020

User Experience Design Essentials

University of California, Santa Barbara

June 2016

Bachelors of Science, Computer Science